so it is week 10 of us trying to make
history trying to turn one of these $100
into a million dollar obviously we tried
to do it in 60 days and that didn't
happen cuz obviously it's week 10 and we
haven't completed the challenge but it's
okay because everything has been
documented here on my YouTube Instagram
telegram Discord everywhere so you guys
not only follow along the journey but
you guys learn from my trades as well
we've made hundreds of mistakes we had a
bunch of lessons and then on top of that
we've obviously had big profits with
following the set and forget strategy we
started 9 weeks ago where I blew the
first attempt and now we are in the
second attempt and this week we're we're
going to try and flip the account and
make back any losses that we had in the
last weeks so let's let the series
[Music]
begin we won't be needing this this week
not breaking in case in glass cuz we're
turning these 300K to I think about 5
600k by the end of this week let me show
you the account balance starting for the
week we are currently at
3:09 you want to know what have been lit
would have been at 305 get it Miami 305
no whatever the point is that it's so
much easier for me to turn these 300K to
600k than it was for me to turn 100
bucks to 1,000 bucks I want you guys to
understand we are in the percentage game
business we're not in the money game
business meaning I'm not focus on the
amount of money that is being turned
into I'm focusing on the amount of
percentage that I'm getting the return
on the money if you think about it if I
turn 100 to 1,000 that's 900% if I turn
300K into 600k that is just 100% It's
Time 1 versus time 9 me turning a 100
bucks into 1,000 is far more impressive
than turning 300K to 600k I want you
guys to keep that in mind and later in
this video I'm going to give you guys
the psychological barrier that a lot of
you guys are struggling through to
actually understand this I'm going to go
very deep into the mindset that I have
to fully fully understand this with that
being said let's get into the technicals
so before anything we got Bitcoin you
guys know I've been looking at Bitcoin
for quite some time and my predictions
on bitcoin are bullish and I believe
we're pretty much ready to go I believe
we are retesting this zone right now we
retesting this inverted left head right
shoulder I do believe this is the Zone
where we can potentially have a solid
Bull Run coming very soon we have
elections coming next year we have the
end of the year wrapping up but
technical wise it is looking decent
right I am not a Bitcoin expert but what
I do notice is technicals I am going to
be looking for potential entries around
this level I called this push I called
this push now I'm potentially calling
this push if we don't hold up around
this area I think we could dip down back
around 24,000 to then have a push to the
upside if not all the way back down to
about 18,000 before having to pchas the
upside but this is not my strong I'm
just looking at this CU I do want to buy
Bitcoin longterm but let's start with
the actual FX markets for this week so
first and foremost audcad audcad we have
the Sals that we have been catching last
week and the sells that we missed last
week but we called perfectly we called
this beautiful break breaking retest
beautiful break and retest all this was
in last week's 100 to the mill challenge
which I missed but I called it perfectly
in the series now this Sunday swings I
literally caught these cells earlier
this morning as of right now we are
currently 11:13 at night Sunday night so
this obviously happened a little bit
earlier but I don't think this trade has
gone just yet if you notice We're
retesting The Zone once again retesting
the Zone once again and now once again
so obviously we are rejecting this very
strong level of support and resistance
we are having the rejection from it I'm
going to be waiting in order to take
this trade for a pullback in order to
buy it so I'm going to need a pullback
now during London session in order to
take the sell or pull back into here in
order to actually enter the sell on this
trade because this is looking very good
to have a huge downside potential for
the rest of this week to fill that
Weekly Wick next we got USD CAD which is
a very simple day trade that we can
catch the same fill the wick so as you
can tell we have strong level of support
support support support support
resistance so now we're just simply
using it as resistance also around
psychological level 13500 or 35,000 I'm
going to be waiting for price to dip
into this area once again and then as
soon as we do that then wait for a shift
to structure on the lower time frame
which will pretty much be this right
here we're going to wait for the push
break retest and then sell and then if
not we're just going to wait for the
break the retest so then we sell I need
to confirm that we are rejecting these
time frames and having a shift structure
at this area in order to cash the trade
to the downside this trade as of right
now we are very bearish on The Daily
very bearish on the 4our and then the
weekly is overdue a pullback the weekly
looks like it's potentially creating a
left head and then a potential right
shoulder to keep going to the upside so
this is a counter Trend trade against
the higher time frames keep that in mind
but what matters is that there's plenty
of room to fill that right shoulder we
can make money on that pullback and then
make money on the buy to the upside so
we're we're going to keep this in mind
for USD CAD this week next we have nzd
JPY as you guys can tell we caught this
trade last week beautiful left head
right shoulder we broke out of the head
and shoulders take profit perfectly this
was literally everywhere this was all
over my telegram all over my YouTube all
over Discord everybody caught this trade
alongside with me and I think this week
we're going to catch it once again
weekly time frame is clearly bullish
four daily time frame is bullish 4our
time frame is so you guys can see here
the daily time frame I expecting for
price to have a retest of this zone
right here it's a very strong level of
support very strong level of resistance
support resistance now we just need a
little quick retest in order to take the
trade to the upside if you guys can see
here I have my alarm set up at the top
of this structure point which almost is
around psychological level of 87 900 so
I'm going to wait I'm going to be
waiting for this price to pretty much
give me a pull back into this area to
then take the trade to the upside I'm
not interested in this counter trend
trade because the majority of the
markets are bullish so I'm only
interested in buying the trade I don't
want to sell so I'm going to wait for it
to come here so then I could get my
solid buy to the upside so this is
nzdjpy next we have audjpy which is
basically the same thing we've had a
very clear breakout if you guys go to
last week you guys can see last week I
drew out these two zones I said we're
either going to break out to the upside
and buy or we're going to break out to
the downside and then sell but we are
going to break out to the upside because
the majority of the time frames are
bullish this is the key to success in
trading the trend is your friend so
pretty much what I'm waiting for this
week is I'm waiting for price to come
back down create a say higher low retest
the EMA retest round psychological level
9500 and then I'm going to take the buy
pretty much how we did here we literally
broke retested push so now we literally
did the same exact thing we had the
break now I'm waiting for the retest
waiting for my shift to structure and
then I take the trade to the upside so
right now we're simply waiting for this
pullback to make it all the way to this
point right here so we're like halfway
there so we got a little bit more room
to go next we got Euro AUD which was our
last profit for last week simple trade
but this has to be I have to wait for a
daily Candlestick so daily time frame I
have to wait for a daily body
Candlestick closure under I have to wait
for a quick retest so then we take the
sell to the downside you can tell we
have one two three four five so it's a
very well respected level of support and
resistance we got to wait for a body
close under a retest and then a sell so
this trade makes sense and this is where
we would be looking for our entries on
the 4H hour time frame 1 hour time frame
Etc and then last but not least Euro JPY
which is looking decent but not even
going to spend time on this we're just
focus on the other pairs that matter so
with that being said probably
information overload but if you guys
have been tuning into this series for
the past 8 weeks you would no we do this
every single week every single week so
as of right now it is currently 11:00 at
night we'll probably you know take a
quick nap and then we're going to wake
up for London so we can catch some quick
trades in London if not see you guys in
New York session all right what's up
guys so it is currently Monday morning
it's 10: in the morning so I woke up
probably like an hour ago obviously woke
up a little bit late because I was up
all night during London session and it
sucks there's probably one thing that I
haar that's wasting time and especially
sleep cuz I got a little bit of sleep so
I stay up all them trying to catch a
trade and and then I come here in the
morning and it's pretty much pulling
back now during New York instead of
during London so you know stayed up
during London for no reason but let me
show you guys right now where we are
this is currently the account we're
still at the same exact starting balance
so let me show you guys what I was
expecting last night so last night on
AUD CAD we were expecting for price to
pull back come into our alarm hit it to
then head to the downside so we enter
the trade pretty much price from where
it was at after it dropped it just kept
dipping down but I do believe that this
is going to going to have the pullback
now during New York session and I do
think later tonight during London it can
have the push to the downside I'm very
very confident in this trade like I
mentioned earlier this week I said we
were going to fill the weekly
Candlestick that's what we're currently
doing right now currently filling it but
in order for me to enter this trade I
have to enter at the lower high so I got
to wait for it to pull back next we got
USD CAD so USD CAD we've been waiting
for it to either make it to our area of
Interest or have the break and retest
under this little zone right here and
that's basically what we're doing right
now and we're having a nice rejection
Candlestick so I'm going to see if this
Candlestick closes how I wanted to in
the next 7 minutes you guys can see
There's 7 minutes and 32 seconds left in
this Candlestick because if this
Candlestick closes under that zone then
it'll be a clear indication but if it
closes above then it can just reject how
it's done here in the past so we're
going to be waiting for this to enter
this trade but it's looking pretty solid
can't even lie uh next we have AUD JPY
so we're we kind of getting this
rejection not from where we want it
though we want this rejection a little
bit lower we want this to be at
9500 not
95200 where it's currently having the
rejection from so this one we're just
sitting on our hands as well Euro AUD
we're having the beautiful rejection how
we expected earlier this week but I
can't take this trade because I'm
waiting for the body to close under now
we're going to wait for the lower high
so then we can enter the trade on this
pair which is looking very very solid um
this probably is going to turn into like
my top one pair depends if the daily
close is how I wanted to uh next we have
your JPY but that'll be something for
next week so oh and we missed nzd JPY so
nzd JPY where were waiting for price to
pull back all the way to here to take
the trade we never pulled back so never
took the trade uh retested really fast
off of this first structure point and
now we're just going to keep watching it
we can't enter you know train that's
already gone we got to wait for it to
stop once it stops then we enter again
so we keep going with the trend so I
will update you guys in the next hour or
two see whatever the market does and
I'll keep you guys posted all right so
trade out there right now it is
currently 10:30 at night Monday night
and our alarm just hit on USD CAD
because we missed it earlier this
morning with what I was expecting just
to show you guys right now on the
account we're pretty much exactly in the
same spot haven't taken any trades so
let me show you guys what I'm predicting
to do London tonight I'm going to
purposely stay up all during l and then
we're going to go hit the gym right now
at 2: in the morning so I'm going to
take a quick nap and I'm going to wake
up right before London session trade and
then go hit the gym so I can stay up and
manage and trade let me show you guys so
this is currently right now USD CAD so
as you guys can tell earlier this
morning I was anticipating a break of
the Zone in order to take it earlier
this morning we were expecting for price
to have the rejection from here and then
we were going to enter at the retest of
that zone we had a perfect retest we had
a perfect rejection from the EMA didn't
take the trade because once again if you
look down here this is not our session
at the time that we take the trade so we
literally let it just have a quick push
and now it's having the pull back into
the area of Interest as I'm anticipating
it's almost following this line that I
drew right here if you notice I'm just
moving it to the left it had the push
perfectly now it's having the retest how
I'm anticipating it so I'm going to wait
for my entry signal at this area AUD CAD
never came back to retest our zone so I
had the dip throughout all of New York
session I do believe we can still pull
back and if we do come back into around
this area here here I will be interested
in taking sells to the downside so this
trade we missed it never pulled back was
never able to take it nzdjpy same thing
never pulled back all the way was never
able to take it audjpy didn't make it to
the area that I wanted to so I didn't
take it and then last but not least Euro
AUD so Euro AUD if you guys look at the
daily time frame it's had the body daily
Candlestick closure exactly as I've been
anticipating we body closed under so now
I'm going to wait for this quick little
Wick retest to retest The Zone notifies
that it's retest the very strong level
of support support resistance and then
resistance zone so this is where on the
4 Hour it's going to be creating a
perfect lower high in order to take this
trade to the downside so this is pretty
much what we're anticipating right now
and those are going to be the top two
pairs for me as of right now it's going
to be Euro AUD pullback to then sell and
then it's going to be USD CAD for entry
signals right at this area basically
where we are right now so once again
update it is currently 10:31 Monday
night and then the account currently has
no active trads so we'll check back in
they're in
London all right so trade update let me
show you guys what's the
deal all right so right now currently
12:00 at night so it's midnight right
now we're currently waiting for hero AUD
to pull back to the area of Interest so
it's actually on the way there from the
last thing that we saw it so it's pretty
much on the way to pullback USD CAD is
at the area of interest that we wanted
to now we're getting the rejection that
we need in order to enter this trade so
we'll probably get this entry signal
right around like 2:30 3: in the morning
how we get usually every single night so
you see we have a 30 minute rejection
from the area of Interest so now we're
going to wait for the bearish and goling
so as of right now midnight yo my
neighbors hate me bro but
forget
actually I can't do like a pool in first
gear I got to do it in second gear with
traction control on and it will still
spin but I'm going to do it just for the
pop so you guys can hear the pop so look
first
gear
second
[Music]
like
that that's how you pull up in sty all
right just to show you guys commitment
is real I'm telling you we're going to
pass this challenge I'm doing everything
1: in the morning right now we're at the
gym because I'm not going to lately I've
been falling asleep and I barely wake up
from London so I'm not making excuses
this week so it's 1: in the morning
right now look at the trade you guys can
see how it is literally rejecting our
area of Interest exactly how we wanted
to right now so we're going to be
waiting for this next Candlestick to
close in the next 8 minutes to see if
it's the entry signal that we need in
order to take the trade but bro
commitment to his finest 1 in the
morning getting a pump Trader lifestyle
cuz we can not that big right now but St
to forget empty
Pockets empty right so this weighs
probably like 2 extra lb
186 this is this is the lightest I've
been in I think a year I used to weigh
200 now I'm going to lean probably down
to like 180 and go back up to
200 yo you want know what's crazy that's
that's traction
on
all right so it' be like the nights at
tonight that are brutal that they get to
me and it's just like annoying and this
is where a lot of Traders they fail
because they feel like they're entitled
to getting profits in the markets
they'll be watching a currency pair or
whatever Market all night all day
waiting for it to come to a certain area
of interest and just because they waited
all that time at least looking at the
chartwise they think that just because
once price gets it they have to take a
trade and that is not the case Traders
think they're entitled to it they think
the market owes them something for the
work that they put in I am tired I think
I've slept two hours and all of that was
for no reason I didn't take the trades
the trades never gave me the entry
signal and that's it it is what it is
this is where a lot of Traders fail
because they're not willing to put the
ego to the side and be like you know
what even though I didn't sleep all
night even though I waited a day and a
half for this even though gave me
everything buil my entry signal not
going to take a trade it's not worth it
this is what's going to separate you
from being an unsuccessful Trader to a
successful Trader so look let me show
you guys this is my Instagram last night
so you guys can see this is my Instagram
this is literally 6:00 in the morning
when we were posting these trades I
literally said no entry signal no trade
this one we're back at our area of
interest and now we're going to be
waiting for a shi of structure to enter
this trade right now at least there was
other traders that caught other trades
at 6:00 in the morning as well so you
guys can see that this is where the work
comes in the dedication the consistency
and doing this time and time again even
if you miss the trade doesn't mean
you're not going to stay up now tonight
in London session cuz you think you're
going to miss the trade again or the
Market's not going to give you the
opportunity to enter the trade this is
what's going to separate you from being
successful to unsuccessful just because
you got one night that it was for no
reason are you just going to let that
get to you and not you do it again you
let that decide for me I'm going to do
it again and again and again and again
cuz that's what's going to separate you
from being successful tonight so let me
show you guys what the market is doing
right now currently as of right now the
account
still no trade so this is how the market
is currently right now still haven't
taken any trades so let me show you guys
what I'm doing on the market right now
so let me show you guys so as you guys
can tell this is USD CAD so we've been
waiting for price to pretty much pull
back into this area of Interest here if
you notice no rejection no bearish
engulfing if you're looking to enter a
trade we need a bearish engulfing
bearish engulfing bearish engulfing we
never had one right here so we simply
never took the trade Euro AUD on the
other hand is is literally I'm going to
take this trade right now I'm going to
literally take this trade right now I'm
going to wait for oh man I don't even
know I should wait yeah you know what I
got to wait I'm going to wait these 12
minutes for this candles stick to close
nah bro I don't even think I can wait
yeah you know what let's wait we're
going to wait these two minutes all
right so we're going to wait these two
minutes right here then you [__] even
glitch whoa
whoa whoa right now say don't wor about
some fire shit's about to go down so
Euro AUD we're going to wait for this
Candlestick to wait to close in 2
minutes and that's where we're going to
pretty much enter the trade if not we'll
wait for the quick pullback um next you
know we're going to kind of just set
that up right now have a 35 pip stop
stop will be pretty big nice next we
have AUD CAD which is on the way back to
the area of Interest so pretty much
headed back to where we wanted to
earlier this week um and then yeah
that's pretty much it so we're going to
wait for this to still break and retest
under and then we're going to wait to
enter this pretty much very shortly so
I'll keep you guys updated on the trade
but make sure you guys don't forget that
don't feel like you're entitled to the
market just because you put in some time
into it the market does not care you
have to keep doing it again and again
and again until you start seeing results
all right so I think it's like 10
minutes later 15 minutes later you guys
are seeing how we're taking this trade
together so let me show you guys so
we're obviously in the trade right now
this is currently how we're sitting on
the account so we took up probably the
biggest loss I've ever taken and you
guys can see how I explained how I was
going to wait for this Candlestick to
close cuzz I needed that quick retest of
price to come back if you guys go down
to the lower time frame it's exactly
what I explained the break the retest we
entered perfectly at that retest cuz I
just I was literally just sitting here
in front of the computer just like this
just looking at if I was if i' been up
all night not about to just not sit here
for 5 minutes and look at it real quick
so I could have slept all night didn't
have to do all that and just woke up
right now at 9:00 in the morning just
got in here and
but we're we're we're in the trck you
know what I'm saying um currently up
11k I mean what do you never mind 9k
what do you expect it's 181 lot trade
this is a 30% risk of the account and
we're going to hit a little set and
forget for now I might add a position
very soon we're just going to wait for
that so in order for us to add the
position we're going to wait for this
we're going to wait for this Candlestick
to like close under strongly so we're
going to wait for this 1 hour to close
under as strong as it can in the next 23
minutes and then after these 23 minutes
I'm going to see if the next hourly
Candlestick is going to give us a pull
back into that level to then take the
trade to then the downside so I will
update you guys throughout the day all
right so it is currently 12:00 in order
to take this trade right now looking
very very solid I'm going to be waiting
for this trade to play out uh looks
decent very confident it let me show you
guys how it is currently looking so this
is how the account is currently looking
right now so we're in the trade right
now at 12:00 so exactly what I explained
which was the pull back to the area of
Interest after this 1 hour body close
we're going to enter at the retest of
the pullback so we didn't enter
perfectly up here again but we entered
pretty much at the closure of that body
which is where we currently are right
now and uh yeah we're just going to hit
a little s and forgot on this trade let
it keep going all right so market update
this is how we're currently looking on
the account we're down about 19,000 so
trade is pulling back um waking up all
night waking up early was pointless but
I'm going to still keep holding at least
the bigger position might close the
smaller position and a loss so let me
show you guys this is currently how
we're looking on the account we're down
about
$118,000 so this is the position right
now we're having a pullback to the area
of Interest retesting under this Zone as
of right now and then we are having a
rejection on the lower time frames here
a little bit I don't like how the daily
time frame is right now the daily time
frame manages well actually never mind I
like it now as long as the daily time
frame does not body close above that
line right there I think it's good but
we have about 36 minutes in order to be
able to tell and uh we have no other
option than just waiting if this 4our
Candlestick can body close under that
line as well that would be extremely
solid and I'll continue to hold this
smaller position I think the bigger
position is definitely safe for downside
potential I just think the smaller
position is risk of hitting stop loss so
for now we're going to keep holding the
position and just s forget so market
update it is currently 8:13 at night so
pretty much almost stop- loss hit my
theory of price pretty much rejecting
the area of how I am expecting it is
happening the spawner position was this
close to hitting stop- loss and now we
are currently up so let me show you guys
how it's F all right so trade update not
as not as I wanted to to the trade
update so we hit stop- loss on the first
trade we almost hit stop loss right now
on the second trade so let me show you
guys
this is how we currently are on the
account right now so we lost the first
trade which is about 20K now we're in
the second loss right now that we're
pretty much about his stop loss I was so
confident on this trade luckily I didn't
add any more positions I was already you
know pretty high leverage so let me show
you guys right now where we are so
currently right now this is how we're
looking on the account we pretty much
almost hit stop loss on the second trade
actually on the first trade we hit stop
loss on this trade right here so this
trade hit stop loss right there um we
looked very we looked very solid
beautiful 1 hour bearish engulfing
beautiful 2hour rejection Candlestick I
didn't like how that Candlestick
rejected but had to keep set and
forgetting um I still like how this
trade looks I just need to wait for it
to pretty much just go down or if it
goes up I'm completely wrong there's
absolutely nothing that I can do on this
trade currently right now USD CAD it is
looking decent we have a level of
support support support we're retesting
it I would not be interested in any
shorts anytime soon I need to wait for
this trade trade in order to take it I
would need for it to have a rejection
like this and then for it to have a
pullback in order for me to take it so
USD CAD not interested for now AUD CAD
never came back and retested the area
how I wanted to it just pretty much
continued to dip so I missed the entry
here missed the entry SE here and the
entry there and then pretty much nzdjpy
do believe it's either going to reject
this area that we are right now or we're
going to reject this area down here so
we're going to wait for it to p pull
back to either or and that is pretty
much it other than that we have audjpy
which is coming in to dip to this area
of interest to retest the round
psychological level
95,000 I'm not really super interested
in it right now I'm just waiting for it
to reject this level potentially give us
some entries but this trade right here
is just just annoying me like it's you
want to know what annoys me that I
stayed up all night for it for no reason
when I took it in the morning it was in
good profit came back back into draw
down went back into profit then almost
stopped me out back into profit and I
almost stop lost again so I pretty much
wasted all all last nightly for no
reason and I might have to even do it
today again so I'll keep you guys
updated in the loop and so I forget
apparently right now it is midnight on
Wednesday well technically Wednesday
morning but it's midnight Tuesday so
Wednesday morning so we'll update either
later during London or tomorrow in the
morning so try to update I don't even
think it's been 5 minutes stop loss got
officially hit so we're currently right
now at a quarter Millie so we're at
$254,000 so pretty much the loss that we
had was about $55,000 loss I was risking
around 55k to make roughly 150 175 so
obviously a positive risk for reward
brutal um I I don't mind staying up two
three nights if I'm obviously going to
hit take profit I'm sure nobody else
would mine like anybody would do that
it's pretty much a no-brainer but I
don't I want to Revenge trade I don't
want to get any type of emotional
because I'm an unemotional type of
Trader I have a very cold approach I'm
very logic I just stick to the strategy
so going to stay out I'm going to rest
tonight catch some sleep tomorrow in the
morning I might just miss London I mean
New York session as well uh even if this
week we don't end up in profit it is
what it is I'm I'm going to make sure I
don't blow this account we we're not
going to come this far just to come this
far so we're going to keep going but I
can't blow it I'm going to make sure I
stay within my strategy and the risk
management rules so I'll update you guys
tomorrow in the morning s and forget all
right what is up guys good morning so it
is currently 11:30 in the morning so
this is pretty much the next morning
from last night so pretty much rested I
woke up like 2 hours ago I just been
looking at the market and this is the
classic example of getting Wicked out in
the market and this shows you guys that
there's nothing that you can do about it
you just literally have to stick to your
plan set and forget and just have a
clear mindset I'm going to explain to
you guys how if I would have had a clear
mindset I would have caught in this
trade right here so let me show you guys
so this trade right here is what we just
got Wicked out last night you guys can
see how it Wicked this out perfectly and
after wickness out it then went straight
into our takeprofit Zone this was right
at the area where we got stopped out
last night right around midnight pretty
much had the continuation up for the
rest of London and New York session has
pushed it down pretty much the highest
point we would have been in profit if
obviously we would have not gotten
stopped out but it is what it is if I
would have had a clear mindset I would
have probably entered this trade
somewhere around up here or even in the
push of this trade but since I had the
clouded mind because of these losses I
completely missed it so the trade was
wicked out but still kept going to the
upside next we have nzd JPY so we had
the retest of this area to go along but
really not paying attention to it USD
CAD not having the rejection that I
wanted to and then audcad just you know
pretty much kept going to the downside
so everything is pretty much just doing
its thing the only one that interests me
right now is AUD JPY which is looking
very very solid because we're having the
rejection from 95,000 the area of
Interest pretty much everything that I
would need in order to take this trade
but I'm not 100% right now because it's
my mindset is not there in order to be
able to trade for this week I'm just
like mentally drained but if I were to
take this trade which it does look
pretty decent now I'm looking a little
bit more into detail I would be waiting
for something like this in order to
actually take it a pull back here in
order for me to take this trade to the
upside so I'll keep you guys updated I'm
going to keep my eye on it but I want
you guys to understand how me not having
the right mindset has completely messed
up this trade for me like because I was
two days without sleeping I was a whole
day just watching a trade go up and
profit back to break even back to profit
and a loss all of that was just messing
my mindset it wasn't giving me Clarity
with what the trade was doing and where
I was with the challenge and that got me
mentally drained so when I finally took
the loss I was like bro you know what
I'm done 2 days of no sleep watching
price fluctuation I'm just done you know
mentally I'm drained got some sleep and
if I would have not been mentally
drained if I would have had my aame with
my mindset good I would have probably
caught in this trade right here and then
you know we would have made back the
losses and probably plus more so this is
a perfect example that I want to show
you guys that once your mindset is out
and once your mindset is not clear it's
done literally you can consider the
account blown you can consider your
chall failed if you don't have the right
mindset it's a wrap it's just simply not
going to happen so this is a perfect
example of how it happened to me right
now and it's another lesson that I've
learned in this journey of turning uh
these hundred bucks into a mail like
it's it's it's been a never- ending
journey and I am still mentally drained
cuz those first two days are brutal and
not going to lie I haven't slept a lot
in the last nine weeks since I've been
doing this challenge so just wanted to
bring awareness to that and uh it's a
little reflection on the reality of the
situation but I'm going to see if I can
get some more rest disconnect a little
bit come back later in the afternoon or
maybe even tomorrow to see if there's
some good trade opportunities but for
now set and forget just to show you guys
everything matches up this is the
current account balance of the account
you guys can see how the pnl here goes
up we've currently had that dip so
obviously today we lost about 70% of the
account it was a $55,000 trade we're
about 33 trades into this account so we
still obviously have a profitable month
and obviously have a profitable year but
we're just going to keep going and try
to scale this account try to bring it
back to where we were and obviously
scale it from that point but this is
currently where we are in the p& chart
all right so trade update well
technically just market update I've come
to the conclusion that I am done trading
for the week um sucks because we kind of
lose the winning streak that we've been
this whole entire time and it kind of
you know messes up the goal of when I
was supposed to complete the challenge
but I I I just realized that I need to
have Clarity in order to complete this
Challenge and I don't need to take these
trades this week in order to come back
and make back those profits I'm just
going to accept the loss for the week
and move on so let me show you guys it's
currently where we're going to stay off
for the week so at
$254,000 I'm going to still be
predicting the market just so I stay in
sync with the market I will never not
look at the market but I just won't
trade right and even me looking at the
market and still having that
self-control of potentially predicting a
trade and not taking it that right there
is the
psychological experience that you get
over time and that I've gotten that
makes me more confident coming back next
week but since I broke the rules since I
was very emotional and I was like just
not focused in the trade I was just more
focused on the money I need to now hold
myself accountable for the mistakes that
I did that is by not trading this week
and you know what sucks can't keep
trading because you know I can't keep
the winning streak going but I I know
this is going to play out positive in
the long run so let me show you guys
this is currently the account right now
I mean the uh the trade right now so
this the same exact Euro AUD trade so
obviously we've been clearly
consolidating at the zone for quite some
time we've had a beautiful daily dogee
rejection Candlestick under the zone
right here very clear daily dogee and
obviously the next day is pretty much
destined to fill all that I do believe
this time frame is going to keep going
to the downside I could clear I can see
extremely clear indications of this
heading down I can see price having here
and then pulling back to the upside and
then heading to the downside I can also
even see this right here having a break
of this area and then retesting it as
well so we can also even see a break and
retest here to continue the sells so
that's what I'm predicting for this week
nzdjpy we're having the reaction from
the area but wasn't interested in it cuz
we can either react from here react from
this Zone USD CAD we're having the dip
as I anticipated earlier as well if I
were to take a trade I'd pretty much
just wait for the retest of this area to
then go to the downside and then AUD CAD
pretty much a trade didn't come retested
and we've just completely melted so
missed entry One Missed entry two three
and four never present itself and last
but not least a UD JPY which we were
looking for buys once this price had
this higher high I was expecting for
price to have a higher low pullback for
me to enter the trade we never had the
higher low high I wanted it to so that I
simply did not take the trade even
though we are still looking very solid
and rejecting this round psychological
level
95,000 I still do believe this can head
to the upside but I won't be interested
unless it does something like
this so these are all very real
predictions they're all stuff that I
would still normally take but I just you
know can't take them because I want to
stick to the plan don't want to blow
this account because it pretty much just
throws two almost two and a half months
out the window so we're going to set and
forget we'll check back in tomorrow to
see how these Market predictions are
going what is up guys good morning so it
is currently 10:30 in the morning so
I've been up for about an hour doing
some Q&A on the Instagram with the
Traders and yeah I'm not trading for the
rest of the week it is 100% confirmed
I'm just going to keep doing the trade
updates uh because I want to obviously
stay in sync with the market like I
don't want to not be in sync with the
market and this is where self-control is
at I can be actively watching the market
every single day to just be in sync with
it but not take a trade that's because I
have self-control so let me show you
guys the trades that we were predicting
last night how some of them played out
now and how we're going to continue
going with the market and uh see where
the market Clos off on Friday so it can
give us a good probability traded setups
for next week so we can turn this
254,000 hopefully back up to 3 400,000
and complete this challenge all right so
here we have Euro AUD so obviously the
trend is taking this trade to the
downside this is why you want to keep
trading with the trend just obviously
we've had some Market being very very
very choppy in this Zone but h w to the
upside he WS to the downside back up
back up down before actually having move
that's why the safe trade is pretty much
once we break and retest under this but
nonetheless this shows you that the
trend once it's in your favor you just
have to figure out where to get in
obviously we're used to clean retest
like this and then a quick sell clean
retest like this and a quick sell clean
retest like this in a quick buy this has
just decided to have more than one
retest and that's basically what we got
and worked out but it is what it is it's
part of the process next is nzdjpy we've
had a reaction from this Zone which I
realistically didn't expect it I
expected more of reaction from this zone
right here next we have USD CAD which is
having the push uh from the area and
then now it's having the retest from the
area which is looking solid if I already
be taking this trade this should be of
my interest now but it will not be as
much of an interest as it would be for
audjpy so audjpy last night we called it
pretty much we're anticipating the break
out of this area and the retest we had
the retest under the Zone we would have
to have the retest above the zone so
then go along but I believe this is
going to be a trade that's going to be
of my interest for next week I feel like
for right now it's not going to be that
much of my interest so we're just going
to keep it going how it is right now
we're just going to keep watching it but
if I were to take the trade I'd wait for
Rus here to then go along CU it's where
the most logical trade setup would be so
as of right now this is how we're
sitting on the account we're sitting at
254 ,000 so not amazing but you know we
still have plenty of time to complete
this challenge all right so market
update it is currently Friday and you
want to know what's crazy the week that
I decide that I'm going to cut my
trading week early is where the markets
play out towards the ending of the week
it's one of those weeks and I miss all
of these trading opportunities and you
know what I don't feel terrible I feel
great cuz I you know I have self-control
I've literally held back from you know
getting involved with the market so I
know next week is going to be a
phenomenal week so once again let me
show you guys so before anything let me
show you guys it is currently Friday
12:00 in the afternoon we're going to go
hit the gym right now you guys are going
to come with us and then the account
right now is currently still exactly the
same 254,000 but let me show you the
trade so let's start off with nzdjpy so
we already know all three time frames
are bullish so the probability of it
going up is extremely high we got to
hide the the camera up here cuz we got
the haters so yeah if you guys want to
hide your camera just get a $5 bill and
just go like that but anyways uh yeah so
we got we got all the time frames in
sync everything's going up we're just
going to continue buying with the trend
strategy is breaking retest it's that
simple doesn't have to be more
complicated than the next we have Euro
AUD which it literally Wicked us out two
times hit takeprofit one did what I
predicted again we broke the area you
see it here breaking it you see it
retesting it right there perfectly as I
explained and we had a huge move this
trade ended up moving this whole entire
week a total of 200 Pips so if I would
have had a crazy risk reward ratio we
would have made loads of profits here
but obviously missed out on this trade
because I decided to not take it we have
USD CAD which had the break and retest
exactly how I anticipated and if I get
this line right here and I put it up to
the point this point almost hit exactly
where I drew up my line obviously now I
guess towards the ending of Friday we're
having some huge news this is why we
stayed out of the market and then last
but not least audjpy so we were
predicting this at this zone right here
where we're anticipating a break and
retest to take the trade to the Buy we
had a beautiful break never had the
retest so we never had our entry signal
on this trade so we had the break but we
never came back for us to be able to
enter the trade so we simply missed it
out but once again we understand Market
Direction so the probability of entering
these type of Trades again and again and
again are extremely probable so um it is
what it is this is the first week in the
last8 nine weeks I think we're in that
we've lost the account is negative for
the you know for the for the challenge
um it was decision of mine to stop
trading because I want to have full
clarity and you know what I'm very happy
I did it and uh it's part of the process
I know it's going to make me have a
better mindset and have more logical
decision making coming next week when it
comes to trading and we're going to go
hit the gym now you guys are going to
come with me and then we have a quick
Market recap after that and let's Get
Hype for next
week good how are you uh i' I'd be
better if you're not trying to scam me
on another deal on a jet shut the [__]
up there's literally nobody that's going
to get you better deals than me and I'd
love to watch anyone try
no bro you're doing the same [__] you do
every single time bro I don't understand
I thought we were
friends okay I'm just going to say I'm
just going to say okay yeah know 38 is
cuz the thing is that I'm literally just
going to go pick up some papers and come
back you got me and I I just don't want
to [__] go on a regular flight Bro
[__]
that I mean to be completely honest with
you you're not going to get a better
deal for 6 hours flight time and you're
staying a night like obviously I don't
have to do the whole jet thing I'm just
being like extra as [__] and I wanted I
wanted to have a reason to talk to you
honestly I'm just being
honest you're so [__] bull of [__]
okay yeah know if yeah so yeah you can
you can let this one go this one it's
just out a budget for what I need like
I'm bro I can literally get the papers
facts dude but I'm I just want to do it
for the
video of course of course you want to do
it for the clout it's not for the
clout of course it's for the clout oh by
the way look look by the way look look
answer FaceTime answer FaceTime well
yeah we we call all
that bro fing hate you well thank God
I'm being a [__] real one right now
thank God I mean trust me we can edit
this [__] however we want so going to
make you see I don't no no no no no I
don't I don't I don't no come the
crow like
a
oh no two
Teslas get some
gas Tesla can never you hear that a
Tesla can never so we're super late to
the actual box we're supposed to be
there at
12 it's
1210 cash in it you late how far are we
probably like another 15 20
minutes [__] well being a regular person
would be 30 correct
yo what up look at this guy look at this
guy in the H look at this guy look at
this guy look at this
guy Y
where what's up that's the McLaren or
the the drifting car no no no the
McLaren the McLaren bro the drift car
wouldn't even be able would like make it
this
far now we're on the we're on the way
we're probably like 10 15 minutes no cap
so I want you guys to understand why I
want to get a jet I was just talking
about it with s and I just realized so
it's selling the car for 530k and I
don't want to pay 530 I want to pay 515
so I got him down to 515 and I am
willing to put 20 25k into a jet to just
go over there and come back to see it
and check it out because that's how much
I value the time so I won't pay5 530 for
the car but I'll put 20K into a jet and
if you add those 20K to the 515 I'm
technically paying 535 for the car but
the way how I see it is like bro I just
saved so much time going in the jet to
go see it and coming back that that time
that I saved I could be making more
money or just being more productive and
other stuff so that's how much I value
time so I'm willing to pay less for the
car but I'm willing to over pay for a
flight to go over there just to go see
it because I value the time that I have
so I just realize that right now I'm
like bro wait even though I got him down
to the price that I wanted him to and
I'm overpaying technically if I go in a
jet because a regular person did go in a
regular flight just to go see it but not
us we're Traders you feel me we're you
know Trader livestyle so we value the
time so we're going to go in a jet so I
just realized that right now maybe I'm
not wording it all the right way but I
hope you guys understand the message
like it's not about what I'm paying for
the car anymore right cuz now I'm
overpaying for the car technically but I
just value the time that's why I want
the jet so we're still figuring the
whole jet thing out
[Music]
you want to know what I just realized
who they going to get of a ticket to
look come
who they going to give a ticket to
me treat
lifestyle so that is it for week 10 uh
lots of lessons learned this week you
guys saw the self-control that I had by
simply staying away from the market even
though that I missed other beautiful
Market opportunities I simply decided to
have self-control and stay away from the
markets this is the first week that
we've had a losing week inside this
challenges so we've had a 9we winning
streak for you guys that don't know my
longest winning stre has been 14 weeks
so we almost got there by hair if I
would have kept trading obviously I
would have made back those losses and
been up for the week but I wanted to
have self-control I wanted to be real to
myself and not trade when I'm not
supposed to be trading so if you guys
want to know more about the set foret
strategy if you guys want to know how
hundreds of my students are making
anywhere from ,000 to $1,500 a week
using my beginner set and forget
strategy watch the link in the
description below because it explains
exactly what is set and forget most of
you guys might be confused and these
videos might be too long for you guys to
understand so if you guys want to know
more about the center strategy and what
it actually consists of just click the
link in the description below and I make
sure you guys tune in for next week
where it's going to be week 11 where
we're going to try and turn back this
money that we lost plus more profits so
we can complete this challenge so
appreciate you guys watching all the way
to the end see you guys in the next
video